[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kainji Lake and Lake Chad are considered lakes of this country.", "correct_answer": "Nigeria", "incorrect_answers": ["Niger", "Cameroon", "Chad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ability to perceive the unpleasant taste of bitter is assumed by researchers to have evolved with this function.", "correct_answer": "To protect people from poisoning", "incorrect_answers": ["To help people choose tasty foods to bad tasting ones", "To help people choose foods with more vitamins", "To protect people from overeating"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Batman movies has raked in the least cash during its theatrical run?", "correct_answer": "Batman and Robin", "incorrect_answers": ["Batman Returns", "Batman", "Batman Forever"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the listed NASA probes made the closest approach to the Sun?", "correct_answer": "Helios 2", "incorrect_answers": ["SOHO", "None of these", "Mariner 10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the highest volcano in Asia, and the highest point in the Middle East?", "correct_answer": "Mount Damavand", "incorrect_answers": ["Bazman", "Sabalan", "Taftan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Antiseptic oils are used to treat these.", "correct_answer": "Cuts and insect bites", "incorrect_answers": ["Poor circulation and listlessness", "Heartburn and indigestion", "Colds and congestion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cats only purr when they are happy.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This nation brews and drinks the most varied and numerous collection of beers in the world varying from the popular pale lager to the esoteric appeal of lambic.", "correct_answer": "Belgium", "incorrect_answers": ["The Czech Republic", "Germany", "The Netherlands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bob Barker was the original host of the very first version of the TV hit game show The Price is Right.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What branch of philosophy or metaphysics deals with the study of being and existence?", "correct_answer": "ontology", "incorrect_answers": ["causality", "epistemology", "phenomenology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The last dance at wedding receptions in Poland is Pani Mloda, also know as this dance.", "correct_answer": "Money", "incorrect_answers": ["Jolly", "Groom", "Funny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This character, played by Swedish actress Britt Ekland in The Man with the Golden Gun, is James Bonds female ally.", "correct_answer": "Mary Goodnight", "incorrect_answers": ["Cindy Shortskirt", "Amy Hotbath", "Jenny Trueheart"]}]